hi everyone this is Uya on eya censored
this is my main Channel my backup
channel is eya Matrix news and I will be
uploading this video to the my backup as
well today is the 7th of December 2022.
please subscribe to eya Matrix news as
this particular Channel ey censored is
on the verge of being taken down
I've had two strikes and one more
they'll erase this channel just like
they've done with my other ones over the
last six almost seven years of being on
this platform
so I wanted to say thank you so much to
those of you been praying for me and
supporting me amazing absolutely amazing
and thank you to those who have already
purchased my book
I have a book on Amazon called the
abomination of desolation the
supernatural Bible changes
and you can find this book
um on Amazon only on Amazon in paperback
format I will be creating a Kindle
version soon
for every paperback book that I sell on
Amazon I get eight dollars and 32 cents
this particular book has over 300 pages
in it and over 2 000 Bible changes in it
keep in mind this is so important that
weird things are happening with this
book
some of you know about it just strange
things
um I cannot guarantee that this book
will not
be changed it's just the way that these
lines signs and wonders are happening
but I pray that this book will be used
as a tool to be able to share the truth
about the obvious changes of scripture
so you will find nonsense verses and
um
nonsensical versus
with grammar errors in it
um new words and so forth
with scripture
um verses
some are just the numbers where you can
find the change in scripture and some
verses are literally written out in the
book
and I have Pages for notes so people can
take notes on what they're observing
what they're reading
if you find something really strange
with anything in the book please let me
know so I can take a look at it
the way that these books are done on
Amazon is it print on demand
so I can make edits as needed
so I'm definitely open to your feedback
thank you to those who've already left a
review on Amazon that's really helpful
and I pray again this book will be a
total blessing for you and for you to
share the truth about what's happening
to the Bible
the changes to scripture are obvious and
self-evident at this point
remember we cannot force someone to see
either they see or they don't see and we
need to move along
but the changes again are self-evident
from emoticons dispelling errors to
nonsense versus grammar errors and
doctrinal errors new people words erased
and so forth and on and on it goes
I am using a pen name in my book so just
keep that in mind
and also
I will be creating some other
um
other study guide materials I think it's
really important
so let me know what you think and I
appreciate again your feedback and your
support and your prayers it means the
world to me may God bless each and every
one of you in Jesus name